Guide to the Women's Self-Government Association records, 1915-1968
Women's Self-Government Association records, 1915-1968
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Women's Self-Government Association records, 1915-1968.
37-9-1208
Cornell University Women's Self-Government Association.
15 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Printed Materials, Financial Records, Reports
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes history, constitution, and bylaws; reports, minutes, correspondence, and notebooks of the Association President; reports, memoranda, and pamphlets of the Second Vice President; budgets, financial statements, checkbooks, correspondence, procedures, and reports of the House of Representatives, including the Judicial Committee and the Residence Committee; Executive Committee and W.S.G.A. Council minutes and reports; and subject files concerning student activities, campus organizations, dormitories, program evaluations, faculty committees, and other subjects. Also, Account books for 1938-40.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Women's Self-Government Association was formed in 1917 and succeeded the Sage College Association in having disciplinary jurisdiction over undergraduate women students at Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes history, constitution, and bylaws; reports, minutes, correspondence, and notebooks of the Association President; reports, memoranda, and pamphlets of the Second Vice President; budgets, financial statements, checkbooks, correspondence, procedures, and reports of the House of Representatives, including the Judicial Committee and the Residence Committee; Executive Committee and W.S.G.A. Council minutes and reports; and subject files concerning student activities, campus organizations, dormitories, program evaluations, faculty committees, and other subjects. Also, Account books for 1938-40.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University--Students.
Subjects:
Student participation in administration.; Women college students.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Budgets, ca. 1915-1934 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- By-laws, ca. 1915-1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Judiciary Committee, ca. 1916 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Reports, ca. 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Gray Book History, ca. 1917-1930 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Judiciary Committee, ca. 1917-1926 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Rules, ca. 1917-1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Sun Editor, ca. 1917-1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Cornell Publications, ca. 1919-1943 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Point System, ca. 1919-1938 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- President's Report, ca. 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- President's Report - Sage, ca. 1919-1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Reports, ca. 1920-1921 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Cornell Songs, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Old Committees, ca. 1921-1937 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Drives, ca. 1922 - 1942 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Reports, ca. 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Activities Committee Cards, ca. 1923-1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Council Minutes, ca. 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Chairman of Organized Groups, ca. 1923-1941 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- CURW, ca. 1923-1943 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Chairman of Activities, ca. 1924-1947 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Dramatic Club, ca. 1924-1940 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Judiciary Committee, ca. 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- News WSGA, ca. 1926-1942 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Debate Club, ca. 1927-1934 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- "The Cornell Women's News", ca. 1927 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- President's Report, ca. 1927-1929 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Junior Advisory, ca. 1928-1944 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- "The Cornell Women's News", ca. 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Women's Glee Club Treasurer's Accounts, ca. 1928-1935 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Dormitory Reports - Balch I, ca. 1929-1953 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Dormitory Reports - Balch II, ca. 1929-1951 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Publicity Chairman, ca. 1929-1931 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Women's Glee Club, ca. 1929-1940 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- WSGA Constitution, ca. 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- "The Cornell Women's News", ca. 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Pan-Hellenic, ca. 1933-1945 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- President's Report, ca. 1933-1940 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Cornell Day for Women, ca. 1934-1942 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Cornellian, ca. 1934-1944 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Mortar Board, ca. 1934 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Balch III Accounts, ca. 1935-1967 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Instrumental Club Accounts, a. 1935-1940 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- WSGA Accounts, ca. 1935-1940 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- WSGA Budget, ca. 1935-1939 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Dorm Report - Balch IV, ca. 1937-1954 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- WSGA Budget, ca. 1938-1944 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Budgets, ca. 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Executive Committee, ca. 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Instrumental Club, ca. 1938 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- President's Report, ca. 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Executive Committee Minutes, President's Report, ca. 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Freshman Orientation Committee, ca. 1939-1943 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Comstock A, ca. 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Comstock B President's Report, ca. 1940-1953 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Budgets, ca. 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Cottage Reports (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1940-1946 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Cottage Reports (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1940-1946 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Budgets, ca. 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Dormitory Report - Balch III, ca. 1941-1952 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Budgets, ca. 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Faculty Committee on Student Activities, 1942-1953 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Founder's Day and Fields of Work for Women, ca. 1942 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Freshman Specials Report, ca. 1942 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- President's Report, ca. 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Budgets, ca. 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Activities Council Minutes, ca. 1943-1946 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Cornell for Victory, ca. 1943 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Faculty Committees, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- WSGA Budget, ca. 1943-1947 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Executive Committee Minutes (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Executive Committee Minutes (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- First Vice President' Report (Folder 1 of 3), ca. 1943-1950 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- First Vice President' Report (Folder 2 of 3), ca. 1943-1950 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- First Vice President' Report (Folder 3 of 3), ca. 1943-1950 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Infirmary, ca. 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- President's Report, ca. 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Secretary's Report, ca. 1943-1957 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Activities Council, ca. 1944 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Budgets, ca. 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Dorm Integration Evaluation, ca. 1944-1966 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Food Reports, ca. 1944 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- House of Representatives Minutes, ca. 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- President's Report, ca. 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- WSGA Constitution, ca. 1944-1950 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Budgets, ca. 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Residence Council (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Residence Council (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Second Vice-President's Report, ca. 1945-1951 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- WSGA/Mortar Board Finances, ca. 1945-1961 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Budgets, ca. 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Chaperon Bulletin, ca. 1946-1950 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Dickson V Treasurer's Ledger, ca. 1946-1967 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Dorm Reports - Dickson V, ca. 1946-1950 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Residence Council, ca. 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Budgets, ca. 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Minutes of Executive Committee and House of Representatives (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Minutes of Executive Committee and House of Representatives (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Budgets, ca. 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- C.A.R.E. Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Freshman Mass Meetings, ca. 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Freshamn Orientation, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- History and Rules, ca. 1948-1952 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- House of Representatives Minutes, ca. 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- IAWS Correspondence with other Schools, ca. 1948-1950 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Mass Meetings, ca. 1948-1950 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- President's Report, ca. 1948-1950 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Residence Council Minutes, ca. 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Treasury, ca. 1948-1961 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Bridge Tournament, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Budgets, ca. 1949-1957 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Budgets, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Campus Organizations, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Dickson VI President's Reports, ca. 1949-1952 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Dorms - WSGA Social Coordinator, ca. 1949-1960 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Executive Committee Reports, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Film Service, ca. 1949 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Food Permission, ca. 1949-1951 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Freshman Orientation, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Head Resident's Handbook/Bulletin, ca. 1949-1951 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- House of Representatives Minutes, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Ithaca Social, ca. 1949-1953 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous Information on WSGA Operation, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Publicity, ca. 1949-1955 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Report of S.P.B. Chairman, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Residence Council, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- WSGA Committees, ca. 1949-1951 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- WSGA Training Program, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Activities Points, ca. 1950 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Budgets, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- By-Laws, ca. 1950-1958 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Campus Organizations, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Cornell Strike, ca. 1950 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Compulsory Registration, ca. 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Dormitories: Fresman Information, ca. 1950-1954 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Dormitory Social Reports, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Faculty Committee on Student Activities, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Fall Meeting, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Freshman Orientation, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- House of Representatives Evaluation, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- House of Representatives Minutes, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Refusal letters for Social Committee, ca. 1950-1954 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Residence Council Minutes, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Residence Hall Meetings, ca. 1950-1954 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Social Coordinator's Report, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Special Events, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Special Permissions Board, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Student Council Conduct Committee, ca. 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Training Program, ca. 1950-1954 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Applications, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Budgets, ca. 1951-1954 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Campus Organizations, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Class Councils, ca. 1951-1953 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Executive Committee Minutes (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Executive Committee Minutes (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Faculty Committees, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Fall Mass Meeitng, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Freshman Orientation, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Freshman Vice Presidents, ca. 1951-1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Frosh and Orientation, ca. 1951 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- House of Representatives, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- House of Representatives Minutes, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- House President's Report, ca. 1951-1954 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- IAWS: Conference on Women in the Defence Decade, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Installation Committee for Dr. Mallott, ca. 1951 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Matters; Correspondence, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Public Relations, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Second Vice-President's Report, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Special Events, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Special Permissions Board, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Spring Meeting, ca. 1951 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Training Program, ca. 1951 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Training Program, ca. 1951-1953 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Transfers, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- WSGA Publicity, ca. 1951-1958 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- WSGA Report, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Beta Epsilon Phi, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Cornell Countryman, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Ithaca Girls, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Social Event Reports etc., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Student Faculty Committee Signups, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Applications, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- At Home - Guest list, Reports, etc., ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Balch III, ca. 1952-1961 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Calendar, ca. 1952 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Campus Organizations, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Co-Ed's Creed, ca. 1952 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Committees, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Dormitory Administration, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Formal Dinner, ca. 1952 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- General Reference, ca. 1952 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- House of Representatives Minutes (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- House of Representatives Minutes (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Men's Social, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Miscellaneous, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Miscellaneous, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Miscellaneous, ca. 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Orientation, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Proposed Changes, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Publicity, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Publicity, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Residence Committee Letters, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Residential Halls, ca. 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Risley, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Second Vice-President's Report, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Social Conduct, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Social Coordinator's Suggestions (Jan Peet), ca. 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Social Program, ca. 1952-1956 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Sorority Council Minutes, ca. 1952-1956 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Spring Mass Meeting, ca. 1952 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Spring Mass Meeting, ca. 1952-1954 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Thanksgiving Weekend, ca. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Turnabout Dance, ca. 1952 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- WSGA Secretary's Report, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Apartment Party Committee, ca. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Applications, ca. 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- At Home Instructions, ca. 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, ca. 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Dorm Libraries, ca. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Fall and Spring Officers' Teas, ca. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Head Resident's Manuals, ca. 1953-1963 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Social Chairman Recommendations, ca. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Social Chairman's Report, ca. 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Social Committee, ca. 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Applications, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Carbon Letters, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Cooperative Housing, ca. 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Dorm Reports - New Freshman System, ca. 1954 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Fall Mass Meeting Skits, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Frush Experiment, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- House Representative's Evaluations, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous, ca. 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Residence Committee Minutes, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Social Chairman, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Social Coordinator's Report, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Social Coordinator's Reports, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Women's Dorm Evaluation Sheets, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- WSGA By-laws, ca. 1953-1955 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- WSGA Newspaper Clippings, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- WSGA Policies, ca. 1954-1957 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Advising WSGA Social Committee, ca. 1955-1963 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Committee Minutes (Executive Comm., House of Reps.), ca. 1955-1957 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Coordination with Men's Dorms, ca. 1955 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, ca. 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Correspondence and Speeches, ca. 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Education, ca. 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Freshman Activities Plan, ca. 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Intercollegiate Association for Women Students, ca. 1955 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Invitations, ca. 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Schedules, Standard Operating Procedures, ca. 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Second Vice-President's Report, ca. 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Shingles, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Speeches, ca. 1955 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Vice-President's Dorm Report, ca. 1955 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Wait and Circle, ca. 1955 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- WSGA Procedures, ca. 1955-1957 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Accounts Ledger, ca. 1956-1963 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Social Chairman, ca. 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Vice-President's Dorm Report, ca. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Sorority Council Minutes, ca. 1957-1960 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Committees, ca. 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Correspondence from other Schools, ca. 1958 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Field Counseling Office Notes, ca. 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Panhellenic, a. 1958-1961 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Scrapbooks (Box 6)
- Reports, Residence Committee Minutes, ca. 1958-1962 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Dorm Questionnaires, ca. 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Executive Committee, ca. 1959-1962 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Judicial Reports, ca. 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Judiciary, ca. 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Student Code, ca. 1959-1963 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Suggestions for Panhellenic Night, ca. 1959 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Agendas and Minutes, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Assembly Agenda, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Dormitories, ca. 1960 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Education Chairmen, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Executive Committee, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Executive Committee, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- IAWS, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Judiciary, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Manual for V.P.'s, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Minutes, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Panhellenic Constitution, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Publicity, News Clippings, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Residential Committee, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Selection/Election Forms, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- WSGA of 1960-1961, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- WSGA Social Coordinator, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Candidates for President, ca. 1961-1966 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- News Clippings, ca. 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Program Coordinator, ca. 1961 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Administration, ca. 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Assembly, ca. 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Dining Room Dress, ca. 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Executive Committee Minutes, ca. 1962 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Judiciary, ca. 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- News Clippings, ca. 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Sorority Committee Minutes, ca. 1962 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Sorority Council Members, ca. 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Sorority Key Reports, ca. 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Box Lunches, ca. 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, Residence Council Minutes, ca. 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Dorm Integration, ca. 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Judicial System, ca. 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- News Clippings, ca. 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- News Clippings - Elections, ca. 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Review and Recommendations Report, ca. 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- WSGA Constitution, ca. 1963 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Election Procedures, ca. 1964 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Financial Procedures and Budget, ca. 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Judiciary Procedures, ca. 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Legislative Representatives Election, ca. 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- News Clippings, ca. 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- News Clippings - Judicial, ca. 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- President's Evaluations, ca. 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Residential Council Report, ca. 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Dormitory Integration Committee, ca. 1965 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Minutes, ca. 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Residence Council, ca. 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Residence Council Correspondence, ca. 1965 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- V.P. Selection Committee, ca. 1965 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Penalties, ca. 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Penalities, ca. 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Residence Staff Bulletin, ca. 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Senate Study of the Report of the Commission on Self-Governance, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 60)